Teen love is a killer.
A Mother's Nightmare is a tv movie, crime, mystery film directed by Vic Sarin.
A seductive teen becomes vindictive when her
boyfriend tries to end the relationship.
Vanessa Redman, played by Jessica Lowndes.
Maddie Stewart, played by Annabeth Gish.
Chris Stewart, played by Grant Gustin.
Donald Mojan, played by Jay Brazeau.
Detective Harcroft, played by Eric Breker.
Jake, played by Aren Buchholz.
A Daughter's Nightmare is a 2014 American TV thriller and suspense film starring
Emily Osment, Gregg Sulkin, Paul Johansson and Victoria Pratt.
It was directed by Vic Sarin and it was released in the United
States on May 3, 2014, on Lifetime network.
This movie was filmed in Kelowna, British Columbia, Canada.
The director of this film, Vic Sarin, made eight films in the Okanagan region since he first
came to Kelowna in 2012 to make the Lifetime TV thriller, A Mother's Nightmare.
The film explores themes of depression, mental illness, new student.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.